

Marcus Vinicius

Date of birth: 28 Mar 1995 **Nationality:** Brazilian

CONTACT





(+351) 912981585

912981585 **(WhatsApp)**

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Web Developer | Front-end Developer | UI/UX Designer

As a Full Stack Web Developer with a focus on front-end development, I bring a comprehensive approach to delivering end-to-end solutions. I specialize in modern technologies and frameworks, including JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, and have extensive experience with React.js, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, PHP, and Laravel.

WORK EXPERIENCE

3 JUL 2023 - CURRENT Lisboa

Creative Developer Innovagency

1 FEB 2022 - 23 JUN 2023 Penafiel, Portugal

Web Designer Anca Design Studio

Porto, Portugal

Full Stack Developer WMC Publicidade

São Paulo, Brazil

UX e UI Designer byBnD Informática

2016 - 2018 São Paulo, Brazil

Web Designer Grupo Solví

2016 - 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

Designer Trainee Essencis Soluções Ambientais

2014 - 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

Marketing Analyst Impacto Eletronics

Digital Marketing, Social Media Product photography, creation of packaging artwork, website development, production of product videos

Supervision/Coordination (Graphic Arts) - from 2014 to 2016 Assistant/Operational (Business Administration) - from 2014 to 2016 Assistant/Operational (Marketing) - from 2014 to 2016

2013 - 2014 São Paulo, Brazil

Graphics designer RM Comunicação Visual

Supervision/Coordination (Graphic Arts)

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Porto, Portugal

Full Stack Web Development EDIT School

Website https://weareedit.io/ | Level in EQF EQF level 5

2014 - 2018 São Paulo, Brazil

Bachelor's degree in Advertising and Social Communication FAPC

OM - Faculdade Paulus de Comunicação

Website https://www.fapcom.edu.br/ | Level in EQF EQF level 6

São paulo, Brazil

Front-end Development - Typescript and React.js Rocketseat

Website https://www.rocketseat.com.br/ | Level in EQF EQF level 5

São paulo, Brazil

Front-end Development Alura

Website https://www.alura.com.br/ | Level in EQF EQF level 4

São Paulo, Brazil

Digital Marketing Specialist Com School

Website https://www.comschool.com.br/ | Level in EQF EQF level 5

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

Listening C1

Spoken production B2

Reading C1

Spoken interaction B2

Writing B2

Spanish

Listening C1

Spoken production B2

Reading C1

Spoken interaction B2

Writing B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

UI/UX Designer | MERN Stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS) | Sistemas de Gestão de Conteúdo (CMS): Joomla, WordPress,Drupal | FullStack Developer